[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "Do you like what you saw?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "I like the dress very much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alina Cho"]}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "I think -- you know, we got Alina Cho joining us now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Alina, do you know who the designer was on that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "I mean, I have to be honest, I'm surprised and not surprised.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "As a man who dresses in Jimmy Choo (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "No, it's better than that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jimmy Choo"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 212, "question": "How do you feel about Jimmy Choo shoes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Well, I -- I just -- I was --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jimmy Choo"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "And Anderson?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 320, "question": "How many were watching your first dance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "We did it, we did kind of like --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "How did you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I cannot hear, Piers, at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "What does that mean to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "It's amazing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "So help you, God?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "So help me, God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Are they all geared up and ready to go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "EE: I think they have to be ready to go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "How quickly will he make it and the knock-offs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "I reckon he already has them made.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "What did you think of the slow dance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "The slow dance was awesome.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130121pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "For people at home and they're watching and they're listening, how do you explain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "Oh gosh, it is an awesome feeling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]